rockyouads.com 2008-12-23

# RockYou.com - photo sharing, MySpace slideshows, MySpace codes, MySpace music

## **RockYou! Privacy Policy**

RockYou! recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use http://www.RockYou.com or other web sites owned or operated by RockYou! (the "RockYou! Sites") (collectively or individually "Users") value their privacy. This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the RockYou! Sites. RockYou! provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the RockYou! Sites. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the RockYou! Terms of Use. Your use of the RockYou! Sites and any personal information you provide on the RockYou! Sites remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. 

Please note that any image, video, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the RockYou! Sites becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. 

The Information RockYou! Collects:  
User Provided Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to RockYou! when choosing to participate in various activities on the RockYou! Sites such as uploading images and captions, uploading videos, posting messages in our forums or in the video comments section, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. 

Cookies Information: When you visit the RockYou! Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. RockYou! uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the RockYou! Sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

Log File Information: Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. When you register with or view the RockYou! Sites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

Clear Gifs Information: When you use the RockYou! Sites, we may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from you RockYou! account is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our Users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make RockYou! Site better for our Users. 

The Way RockYou! Uses Information:  
If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the RockYou! Sites, then we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the RockYou! Sites. 

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your display name (not your email address) may be displayed to other Users when you upload images or videos or send messages through the RockYou! Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any images, captions, videos or other content that you submit to the RockYou! Sites may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

We may use your email address for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major RockYou! Site changes, new messages in your inbox, or for customer service purposes). We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the RockYou! Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the RockYou! Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests; (f) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our Users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP; and (g)access you information after you sign in. 

When RockYou! Discloses Information:  
We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the RockYou! Sites. RockYou! May share personally-identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information with third party-affiliates and business partners for the purpose of offering greater functionality and enhanced services through RockYou! or other sites, and for the purpose of communicating these services to you. 

We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 

It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including but not limited to, fraud, potential threats to public safety or the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise permitted by law. 

RockYou! also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally identifiable information that RockYou! believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our the RockYou! Sites, and to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of RockYou!, our Users or others. 

Your Choices:  
You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the RockYou! Sites, in which case RockYou! may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. Please note that media files uploaded by Users to the RockYou! Sites cannot be removed and remain subject to our Terms of Use. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you profile access or making corrections. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

Please contact RockYou! with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy at support@rockyou.com 

Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites:  
RockYou! allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the RockYou! Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the RockYou! Sites. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. 

RockYou! does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks RockYou! to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. The RockYou! privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

Currently, RockYou! has relationships with the following third-party ad servers or ad networks: 

Google, Inc. (http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) Adbrite, Inc. (http://www.adbrite.com/mb/privacy.php) 

Our Commitment To Data Security:  
RockYou! uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to RockYou! and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, RockYou! makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If RockYou! learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. RockYou! may post a notice on the RockYou! Sites if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us using this contact form. 

Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:  
Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, RockYou! does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the RockYou! Sites from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the RockYou! Sites at any time or in any manner. If RockYou! learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the RockYou! Sites without verified parental consent, then RockYou! will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents or guardians for permission before sending any personal information to anyone over the Internet. 

International Users:  
The RockYou! Sites are hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the RockYou! Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the RockYou! Sites, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. 

In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy:  
In the event that RockYou! is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 

Changes and Updates to This Privacy Policy:  
This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the RockYou! Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. 

For revisions to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information. 

Date Last Modified:  
This Privacy Policy was last modified February 13, 2006. 

Contact Information:  
Please contact RockYou! with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or the RockYou! Sites by emailing support@rockyou.com.
